<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lihao (Jasper) Zhang</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lihao (Jasper) Zhang</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 11:52:13 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Donors</title>
      <link>/projects/finding_donors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 11:52:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/finding_donors/</guid>
      <description>Supervised Learning Project: Finding Donors for CharityML Getting Started In this project, you will employ several supervised algorithms of your choice to accurately model individuals&amp;rsquo; income using data collected from the 1994 U.S. Census. You will then choose the best candidate algorithm from preliminary results and further optimize this algorithm to best model the data. Your goal with this implementation is to construct a model that accurately predicts whether an individual makes more than $50,000.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Housing</title>
      <link>/projects/boston_housing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 22:28:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/boston_housing/</guid>
      <description>Model Evaluation &amp;amp; Validation Project: Predicting Boston Housing Prices Getting Started In this project, you will evaluate the performance and predictive power of a model that has been trained and tested on data collected from homes in suburbs of Boston, Massachusetts. A model trained on this data that is seen as a good fit could then be used to make certain predictions about a home — in particular, its monetary value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploratory Analysis with MovieLens Data</title>
      <link>/blog/netflix_movie_recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 22:28:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/netflix_movie_recommendations/</guid>
      <description>1. Load Data into Pandas Dataframe import pandas as pd import numpy as np # pass in column names for each CSV and read them using pandas. # Column names available in the readme file # Reading users file: u_cols = [&#39;user_id&#39;, &#39;age&#39;, &#39;sex&#39;, &#39;occupation&#39;, &#39;zip_code&#39;] users = pd.read_csv(&#39;ml-100k/u.user&#39;, sep = &#39;|&#39;, names = u_cols, encoding = &#39;latin-1&#39;) # Reading ratings file: r_cols = [&#39;user_id&#39;, &#39;movie_id&#39;, &#39;rating&#39;, &#39;unix_timestamp&#39;] ratings = pd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooli’s Hot New Hardware</title>
      <link>/blog/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/third/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article originally appeared in CodeRag.
When Hooli acquired Endframe, no one could wait to see what the tech giant would do with the revolutionary, middle-out compression technology. The wait is over: In a savvy pivot, Hooli took the software and created their newest hardware: the Hooli/Endframe Box. While initially conceived as a consumer-facing platform, the Endframe technology has been repurposed to “make the world a better place through secure, high-capacity enterprise data storage servers utilizing middle-out compression technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Erlich administers the Hacker Hostel, a tech incubator where Richard, Big Head, Dinesh, and Gilfoyle live and work in exchange for 10 percent of their potential businesses. Erlich clings to his glory days, when he sold aviation start-up Aviato, a move that, at least in his mind, qualifies him to be a svengali lording over other tech nerds. He still drives a car emblazoned with multiple Aviato logos and smokes copious amounts of weed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gavin Belson</title>
      <link>/blog/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 15:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article originally appeared in CodeRag.
Gavin Belson’s name has long been synonymous with innovation—but beyond his work at Hooli, do we even know the man behind the rampant success? In a Code/Rag exclusive, Belson revealed to us 10 things about himself that aren’t common knowledge.
 He’s a nature fanatic! “It’s important to me that Hooli has an effective recycling program, and a personal passion of mine is donating to elephant sanctuaries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belson Back on Top</title>
      <link>/blog/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 16:59:13 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/second/</guid>
      <description>Note: This post originally appeared in CodeRag
Gavin Belson’s brilliant leadership is unstoppable. While allegedly taking a personal hiatus from day-to-day operations at Hooli, Belson couldn’t resist brokering a blockbuster deal between Hooli and Maleant Data Systems, deploying Hooli’s innovative new Hooli/Endframe Box. The multi-year deal brings handsome margins for Hooli and can easily be a template to apply across the entire Fortune 1000. An inside source tells me that, no surprise, the board was no longer satisfied to let Belson fade into the background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015-07-23-r-rmarkdown/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>